ERICA LIMA

Montreal-QC, Canada ericasantini92@hotmail.com +1 (438) 920-9806

Linkedin: https://linkedin.com/in/santinidelima/ Portfolio: https://kikasantini.github.io/projects/

SUMMARY

Passionate about technology and coding since childhood. Math and logic are a strength. Took over 3 years of computer science courses and, most recently, worked on a technological environment, managing, coding, documenting, and testing software. Currently studies Programming to pursue career in the area, with graduation due in January 2023.

Also familiar with the Agile Methodology applied to software development. Believes in continuous improvement and learning. Can communicate in Portuguese, English and French.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Imgnation Studios, game development studio in Santa Maria – RS, Brazil.

Producer, February 2021 – December 2021 (11 months)

Managed a 6-people team on a Virtual Reality game project. Performed activities such as sprint planning, game testing, documentation of game features and bugs, quality assurance check-ins and daily meetings.

Project Manager Intern, August 2020 – January 2021 (6 months)

Managed a small team during the development phases of hyper casual games for mobile. Planned the schedule, broke it down on sprints and led the team through it. Performed sprint planning and game documentation using software like Microsoft Word, Miro, Notion and Trello. Investigated and proposed means to improve the development of the projects, with positive results and feedbacks from the team.

EDUCATION

DEC Computer Techniques - New Media Programming, August 2021 - Present

Institut Grasset, Montréal – QC, Canada.

Currently enrolled on the 2nd semester of the program. School report available if requested.

Bachelor Business Administration, March 2017 – January 2021 (3 years and 10 months)

Universidade Federal de Santa Maria (UFSM), Santa Maria – RS, Brazil.

Graduated on time with good grades. Held two consecutive scholarships, in which helped in the development of scientific articles. Was part of a Junior Enterprise, doing consulting projects for over a year.

Computer Science Courses, March 2013 – November 2016 (3 years and 8 months)

Universidade Federal de Santa Maria (UFSM), Santa Maria – RS, Brazil.

Took programming classes, participated in a regional marathon, did voluntary tutoring in Programming Laboratory I and II and participated in the Programming Club, teaching logic to high school students.

Hard Skills

Business bachelor's degree

Broad understanding of programming logic

Programming languages (C, C++, C#)

Image and layout editing (Photoshop)

Agile methodologies (Scrum, Kanban)

Microsoft Office package

Visual Studio (VS), Visual Basic for Applications (VBA) and Unity

Basic GitHub manipulation

Basic VIM manipulation and text editing

Basic scripting (Python)

Windows Operational System

Basic Linux

Typing speed: 66 - 78 wpm

Languages:

Portuguese - Native language

English - Fluent

French – Upper Intermediate (level B2 – CEFR)

Soft Skills

Proactivity
Critical thinking
Adaptability
Organization
Willingness to learn
Effective communication

VOLUNTEERING AND OTHER INFORMATION

COVID-19 Immunization

Vaccinated with 2 doses.

Université du Québec à Montreal (UQÀM), Montreal - QC, Canada.

International Student, September 2019 – December 2019 (4 months)

Took 1 semester of Business Administration at UQAM as part of the bachelor's degree at home university.

Nuzzle & Co. Pet Rescue and Adoption, Park City – UT, United States.

Volunteer, January 2018 – February 2018 (2 months)

Acted as a volunteer taking care of rescued cats.

Catiane Lange Imóveis, real estate company in Santa Maria – RS, Brazil.

Intern, August 2017 – November 2017 (4 months)

Carried out registrations of properties, owners and tenants using ERP software. Collected payments related to rents, performed banking procedures, and updated values accordingly to current rates. Helped planning and improving the company's short-term strategic planning. Non-paid internship.